<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Upside-Down Trees on UpsideDownTrees</title><link>https://blog.mhashim6.me/</link><description>Recent content in The Upside-Down Trees on UpsideDownTrees</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 11:11:11 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.mhashim6.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>9 Rings for Amazon doomed to die</title><link>https://blog.mhashim6.me/rings-of-power/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.mhashim6.me/rings-of-power/</guid><description>For years now Amazon have been working on &amp;ldquo;The biggest fantasy series in history&amp;rdquo;. Yet every year, red flags kept on showing and it always seemed too good to be true. And now that the trailer is here, I can confirm: This show is awful.
I was really looking forward to this show, I&amp;rsquo;ve always been an avid reader of Tolkien&amp;rsquo;s every piece of literature. And the &amp;ldquo;Rings of Power&amp;rdquo; is a rude insult to the world that Tolkien created.</description></item><item><title>Sell yourself now, be freed (maybe) later</title><link>https://blog.mhashim6.me/bnpl/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.mhashim6.me/bnpl/</guid><description>Such a smooth deceiver Grinning as he leaves them Empty handed and broken Feeling like givers not victims – Mike Semesky
Be me: I’ve just completed my Military Service, I had lots of plans, needs, and preparations for my new life. There was this one item that I needed, and much more wanted. And no, I couldn’t afford it.
The scenery I hadn’t enough cash on me, and I wasn’t going to lose all my (puny) savings on it, and waiting is a pretty difficult option.</description></item><item><title>Oneliness</title><link>https://blog.mhashim6.me/oneliness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.mhashim6.me/oneliness/</guid><description>The word &amp;ldquo;Loneliness&amp;rdquo; hasn&amp;rsquo;t always been present in the English language. In fact, it is relatively new. &amp;ldquo;Oneliness&amp;rdquo; on the other hand had always been there, meaning one&amp;rsquo;s being alone. It&amp;rsquo;s considered obsolete now in modern English. But it could be a perfect description of the state of many; There&amp;rsquo;s a case for people who are lonely, yet not alone. And the exact opposite.
Many are familiar with that feeling, summarized as just not being surrounded by the &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; people–people who wouldn&amp;rsquo;t tolerate a talk of opening-up, or people that are not particularly interested, or people who are absolutely compassionate and supportive, but really have nothing to offer.</description></item><item><title>The case for Holidays</title><link>https://blog.mhashim6.me/case-for-holidays/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.mhashim6.me/case-for-holidays/</guid><description>Today is my last day on a week-long vacation. It&amp;rsquo;s a real blessing to have such relatively-long off-work time. And this very fact is a problem!
I remember 3-4 years ago I&amp;rsquo;d often feel sad at the weekend because now I&amp;rsquo;m forced to stop doing the activities I loved, be it college projects, gatherings and believe it or not work. I remember me doing side-projects on weekends as if I was just playing a video game; I&amp;rsquo;d never notice the passing of time, nor the effort I spent on these projects.</description></item><item><title>Bereft</title><link>https://blog.mhashim6.me/sharing-my-sorrow/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.mhashim6.me/sharing-my-sorrow/</guid><description>Why would people share how they feel with the entire world? Is it normal to hang a sign on a central wall saying that Mr.Doe is not happy? It’s quite normal when it comes to family and closed ones. But the entire world?
Now indeed it’s encouraged to share one’s feelings and opinions for everyone to see and discuss. It’s perceived as normal by many. Some say it’s therapeutic. Some accept and welcome the new change and adopt it, following the spirit of trying new things.</description></item><item><title>Why?</title><link>https://blog.mhashim6.me/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 11:11:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.mhashim6.me/about/</guid><description>Why did I make this?
This place hosts writings that are not bound to a specific time, nor a region. It hosts my notions, thoughts, and recordings of my life and labour.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://blog.mhashim6.me/contact/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 11:11:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.mhashim6.me/contact/</guid><description> Don’t fill this out if you’re human: Name Email Message Send</description></item><item><title>Gossips: An Event-Bus in a Chatty Neighborhood</title><link>https://blog.mhashim6.me/metaphorical-programming-gossips-event-bus/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 11:11:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.mhashim6.me/metaphorical-programming-gossips-event-bus/</guid><description>In this post we&amp;rsquo;ll tackle a common issue: simple communication between system components. With a slightly controversial, themed, domain-driven design.
Let&amp;rsquo;s say our project is an Android app, and we need a functionality that requires two fragments to communicate. You know Android, social distancing between components is the norm out there. We&amp;rsquo;ll use this as an excuse to write an Event Bus.
I chose an analogy for the entire thing: Gossips; It fits with the nature of the library, and the way it&amp;rsquo;ll be used–A global pub-sub component to enable cross-component communication.</description></item><item><title>Creating a project amidst a world crisis</title><link>https://blog.mhashim6.me/pm-in-crisis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.mhashim6.me/pm-in-crisis/</guid><description>May, 20, 2020 The past three months were a completely new experience to us; We (13 CSE undergrads) set out to build an Open online Quran reciting and teaching platform.
We didn’t know of the upcoming global circumstances when we planned the project. We haven’t seen each other (physically) in the project’s entire lifetime. Due to social distancing. The project was initially a school assignment. We were to simulate a database project, and the school set the deadline to be 2 months.</description></item></channel></rss>