<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rant on UpsideDownTrees</title><link>https://blog.mhashim6.me/tags/rant/</link><description>Recent content in Rant on UpsideDownTrees</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.mhashim6.me/tags/rant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Oneliness</title><link>https://blog.mhashim6.me/oneliness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.mhashim6.me/oneliness/</guid><description>The word &amp;ldquo;Loneliness&amp;rdquo; hasn&amp;rsquo;t always been present in the English language. In fact, it is relatively new. &amp;ldquo;Oneliness&amp;rdquo; on the other hand had always been there, meaning one&amp;rsquo;s being alone. It&amp;rsquo;s considered obsolete now in modern English. But it could be a perfect description of the state of many; There&amp;rsquo;s a case for people who are lonely, yet not alone. And the exact opposite.
Many are familiar with that feeling, summarized as just not being surrounded by the &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; people–people who wouldn&amp;rsquo;t tolerate a talk of opening-up, or people that are not particularly interested, or people who are absolutely compassionate and supportive, but really have nothing to offer.</description></item><item><title>The case for Holidays</title><link>https://blog.mhashim6.me/case-for-holidays/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.mhashim6.me/case-for-holidays/</guid><description>Today is my last day on a week-long vacation. It&amp;rsquo;s a real blessing to have such relatively-long off-work time. And this very fact is a problem!
I remember 3-4 years ago I&amp;rsquo;d often feel sad at the weekend because now I&amp;rsquo;m forced to stop doing the activities I loved, be it college projects, gatherings and believe it or not work. I remember me doing side-projects on weekends as if I was just playing a video game; I&amp;rsquo;d never notice the passing of time, nor the effort I spent on these projects.</description></item><item><title>Bereft</title><link>https://blog.mhashim6.me/sharing-my-sorrow/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.mhashim6.me/sharing-my-sorrow/</guid><description>Why would people share how they feel with the entire world? Is it normal to hang a sign on a central wall saying that Mr.Doe is not happy? It’s quite normal when it comes to family and closed ones. But the entire world?
Now indeed it’s encouraged to share one’s feelings and opinions for everyone to see and discuss. It’s perceived as normal by many. Some say it’s therapeutic. Some accept and welcome the new change and adopt it, following the spirit of trying new things.</description></item></channel></rss>