<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Archive on UpsideDownTrees</title><link>https://blog.mhashim6.me/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Archive on UpsideDownTrees</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 11:11:11 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.mhashim6.me/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bereft</title><link>https://blog.mhashim6.me/2022/05/03/sharing-my-sorrow/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.mhashim6.me/2022/05/03/sharing-my-sorrow/</guid><description>Why would people share how they feel with the entire world? Is it normal to hang a sign on a central wall saying that Mr.Doe is not happy? It’s quite normal when it comes to family and closed ones. But the entire world?
Now indeed it’s encouraged to share one’s feelings and opinions for everyone to see and discuss. It’s perceived as normal by many. Some say it’s therapeutic. Some accept and welcome the new change and adopt it, following the spirit of trying new things.</description></item><item><title>Gossips: An Event-Bus in a Chatty Neighborhood</title><link>https://blog.mhashim6.me/2020/06/19/metaphorical-programming-gossips-event-bus/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 11:11:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.mhashim6.me/2020/06/19/metaphorical-programming-gossips-event-bus/</guid><description>In this post we&amp;rsquo;ll tackle a common issue: simple communication between system components. With a slightly controversial, themed, domain-driven design.
Let&amp;rsquo;s say our project is an Android app, and we need a functionality that requires two fragments to communicate. You know Android, social distancing between components is the norm out there. We&amp;rsquo;ll use this as an excuse to write an Event Bus.
I chose an analogy for the entire thing: Gossips; It fits with the nature of the library, and the way it&amp;rsquo;ll be used–A global pub-sub component to enable cross-component communication.</description></item></channel></rss>